Let's go.
Come on.
Wait.
We are being followed.
Sir, ma'am,
Where to?
We are not going anywhere.
This car is yours.
Let's go.
This car is mine.
Unbelievable.
Where on earth did they go?
I really don't know, boss.
I don't know.
Boss, I really don't know.
We found them.
Get lost.
Pei Song.
Hello,
Grandpa.
Pei Song,
what have you been busy with lately?
As the saying goes,
there are three forms of unfilial conduct,
and having no descendants is the worst.
You are already thirty,
but you still haven't settled down.
The family has placed such high hopes on you.
I'm telling you,
this blind date,
you must go today
no matter what.
Grandpa,
I've told you so many times.
I'm not going.
I have no interest in marriage.
Hello?
Pei Song.
Okay.
I'll go right now.
This boy
is quite obedient today.
Peining.
You should learn from your brother.
After your brother has a child,
it will be your turn.
Grandpa.
Actually,
I don't want to use social apps
or go on blind dates to get married.
Do you have someone you like?
Not really.
I want
to marry my significant other
because we truly love each other,
not for any other reason.
Your thought
is not unreasonable.
But Peining,
let me tell you,
marriage
is not as simple as you think.
Look at your brother.
He's busy with work all day.
How does he have time to date?
I don't care if your brother
finds someone through a blind date
or finds someone himself in the future.
Anyway,
I want to see my granddaughter-in-law walk through the door today.
Okay.
Grandpa,
have some tea.
Are you
Song Shiya?